Are you here?
[Fansubs by Garfield]
I turned it on.
- Hehe.
We're here!
I made a mistake and I started it vertically.
We're back after all that.
Minju - We're back. clap clap clap
Yujin - It's horizontal now, isn't
Minju. - It's horizontal, right?
- Bye~
Let's pretend we've never seen each other before.
Hi, WIZ*ONE!
(Video on V LIVE) Are you okay now?
There's a huge secret to my clothes. Guys.
Chaewon - What is it?
Minju. - Here you go.
Can you write it for me?
Oh, so cute.
Minju - Cutie~
Tommy. - Cute.
Eugene - Bear has ears.
Eunbi - Soft
It's really soft.
So today, oh, my.
Minju - It's soft. - Haha.
Bear ears.
CHAE WON - So cute.
Minju - It looks good on you.
I like bears these days, right? That's what it is.
Yujin - I tried it on!
CHAE WON - Is that right?
Minju. I like it.
Tommy. - Cute.
You can't see it again if your ears fall backwards (?
MIN JU - Oh, you look so pretty right now. (Kang)
Eugene. - Okay.
Please read the comments.
Eunbi - Yes~
Chaewon - They said I look like Yena unni with bangs.
Minju. - Yeah, you two look like real twins.
Eugene - Uh, it's dark all of a sudden.
Minju - (Agreed) It's suddenly dark.
Tommy. - Oh, maybe it's because I'm in front of you.
Yujin - I guess it's because we're close!
Eunbi - Oh, it's too far(?)
Tommy - Closer
Minju - Is this a focus?
Tommy. Oh.
Eugene - (agree) Yes.
Eunbi - It's a matter of focus.
Do you want me to move the camera a little bit more sideways?
It gets dark when we get closer.
Oh! The person in front of you looks bright and the person behind you looks black.
Tommy. - Uh, isn't that okay?
Eugene. - I'm just fine right now.
Minju, we need to bend down.
Chaewon - I'm sitting like this.
Eugene - I'll be like this.
Minju. - Come on down.Haha
Eunbi - I keep splitting my bangs, like I said yesterday.
Yesterday.
Oh, we're going to perform at the Seoul Music Awards.
I thought I had long bangs, but they split a lot.
And so, I was upset.Hah!
Chaewon and Minju - Tommy's hair is pretty!
(Suddenly?Haha
Tommy. - Oh, really? They say your hair is pretty. Thank you.Haha
Eugene. - What is it?lol
Minju - Doesn't it suit you so well? Everyone? I think short hair suits you well.
Tommy. - And I got my hair bobbed hair.
Chaewon - (I agree) Yes.
Tommy. - Really?
Minju. - Yeah, you look great.
Chaewon - It's totally new.
Tommy - But which one would be better? Long hair?
- Mm-hmm.
Eunbi - I have short hair.
Eunbi - Because it's new
Minju - It's been a while for me too.
Eugene. - That's right.
Yujin - Once I've revealed it!
Eunbi - You were pretty.
Minju - She's always had long hair.
Tommy. - Once you've revealed it?LOL
Yujin - You have to keep your hair short. No, it looks good on you.
Tommy - Uh-huh.
Yujin - It looks good on you, too.
Yujin - You have to do it for a long time when you reveal it. Or else you'll be sorry.
Chaewon - (Eunbi) Unnie's headrest
Eugene - You're gonna be so sorry. Probably.
Minju - That's perfect.
Eunbi - What about me?
- You?
Yujin - But you~
Tommy - I like your bobbed hair.
Yujin - I have long hair and short hair very often.
Minju. - That's right.
Eunbi - I've grown a lot.
Chaewon - All, they both do it often.
Minju - You look good together, but I personally think you look good.
I like short hair.
- Me, too.
Minju - Complete Personal Taste
Chae Won - Different Feelings Completely Different
What's that reaction?
- I'm worried.
I love your short hair.
Eunbi. - What about Yujin?
Yujin - What about me?
Eunbi. - Yujin.
Minju - Eugene?
- Medium shot, Eugene medium shot
Chaewon - I think you look really good with medium-length hair.
Yujin - Really?
Minju - Eugene's perfect for a stop.
Chaewon - Perfect!
Tommy, and I like it when I don't have bangs.
Minju - By the way, it's been a while since I've seen my bangs????
Eugene. - Right.
Eunbi. - Yeah, it feels different.
I have a good time getting off.
Minju - I like the bangs. You don't like it?
- None of them.
Minju - lol. I'much.
No, but when I first got off, I thought you were really pretty.
CHAE WON - That's right.
Minju - But I feel empty without bangs.
Eugene. - Really? I'm so happy I'm not here.
Minju - No, I feel a little empty these days.
Minju. - That's good.
Yujin - Don't you feel comfortable?
Minju. - I love it. But
I'm so comfortable on stage.
Tommy. - It's really comfortable.
CHAE WON - Without bangs, I'm jealous of the fact that I can flip it over on stage.
- That's right.
Minju - That little baby head is a bit of a poke in the eye.
- That's hard. I'm a government official. I'm curly.
- My bangs aren't as pretty as Chaewon.
Chaewon - (Comments) It looks like Chaewon's wig.
- Kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk.
MIN JU - Wasn't it really cut neatly?
Tommy. - He's cute.
CHAE WON - It looks like a real ruler, right?
Eugene. - Totally straight.
Minju. - You've changed your hairstyle, not everyone knows.
Eunbi - Oh, right. It was.
Eugene. - That's right.
Eugene. - Totally. Who else?
Again...
Chaewon - Yena dyed her hair.
Yujin - That's right. That's right.
Minju - Blue Black!
Chaewon - I dyed my hair blue black.
Minju - Chaeyeon has bangs and then she's gone.
MIN JU - SAKURA, I love having bangs.
CHAE WON - (SISTAR song) There is and there isn't.
YU JIN - Didn't SAKURA dye her hair, too?
Minju. - Is that right, Tone Down?
EUN BI - NAKO dyed her hair, too.
Tommy - Dark
Eugene - We dyed our hair a lot.
Chaewon - (Comments) Everything is pretty.
Minju - Tommy, you look so purple on the screen.
- If you look at it like this, it looks like light purple, right?
Tommy. - That's right.
Tommy. - And Hitomi's all grown up. To get here,
clapping clapping
Minju - Wow~
Chaewon - Hitoma~
Tommy - So, this, short hair? LOL
CHAE WON - Congratulations!
Chaewon - You did a great job. Dude.
Tommy. - Thank you.~
Eunbi - Hitomi~ Good for you. Hitomi is still here.
Chaewon - That's amazing. How can you do that?
CHAE WON - Hey, this is how time went by.
Minju. - I know.
Minju - I can't wait to grow them.
Tommy. - That's how much I've had. Like Eunbi unni right now?
Eugene. - Right.
Tommy. - But it grew all the way here.
CHAE WON - Wow, you've grown a lot.
Eunbi - You've grown, haven't you?
Minju - You've really grown up.
Eunbi - It looks like you've grown a little bit, right?
Chaewon - Grow up.
Tommy. - I used to spray a lot back then.
Tommy. - You, too. You, too, right?
Eunbi - Yeah, spray.
Minju. - You can't see it.
CHAE WON - Press it like this
Eunbi. - Spray it.
Minju - That's uncomfortable.
Minju - When will my hair grow?
Eunbi - It's short to tie your hair.
Tommy. - Minju keeps on going.
Minju - Why do I feel the same hair for a year?
Chaewon - Why isn't your hair growing?
Minju - It's not growing. Let me grow up.Haha
Chaewon - What's wrong with your back hair?
MIN JU - What's wrong with your back hair?
Eunbi - It's short.
Minju-Chaewon, why do you always wear the same t-shirt?
- Pretty~
Chaewon - I love it.~ haha
Eunbi - I want to do it too, will I think about it?
Minju - Oh! You know, like this. You have seaweed on your face. Handsome.
Chaewon - Hey, that's too obvious.
Yujin - When did you do that?
Eunbi - I didn't know.
Minju. - Isn't it like this?
You know that pretty is a bit old, right?
Chaewon - Pretty is old, WIZ*ONE is disappointed!
Minju - Oh really? Oh, I like this kind of stuff.
YU JIN - Did WIZ*ONE do this? It was totally new.
- Kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk.
Eunbi - Let's do that. nonsense
Chaewon - Nonsense?
Eugene - Shouldn't there be someone who's asking questions?
Minju - What if the king falls?
Yujin - King Kong!
Eunbi - Oh, you're good. I need to pay.
- Do you want me to try?
Chaewon - Can you give it to me?
I'm searching for a nonsense quiz.
Eunbi - Should I make it easier?
Minju. - Yeah.
Chaewon - But I can see everything.
Eunbi - Funny nonsense
Minju. - What's there?
Eunbi - What if a person cries?
Chaewon - What if people cry?
Minju - Mermaid. x2 I'm sorry.
Eugene. - Huh? What?
Minju - Urgh?
- What if people cry? Everyone, please guess together.
Tommy. - What are you doing?
Minju - Oh, it's a little... A ridiculous quiz. Same thing)?
Eugene - (Hair) Why is it sticking out?
Minju - (Explaining to Tommy hard...)
Eunbi - I don't think this is right. I don't think I can get it right.
Eugene. - No way?
Chaewon - Is that a whimper?
Yujin - What if I cry? Oh, what the hell?
Minju - (To Tommy) I'll let you know later.
Tommy - haha.
Eunbi - Should I not say no?
Eugene - I'm curious. But, wait a minute.
Minju. - Look at her and... (Something easy)
Eunbi - Oh, okay. (Found it) Do you want to do it?
Eunbi - What car do middle and high school students ride?
Minju - Used Car
Eunbi - Oh~~
Chaewon - Oh, this was easy (?)
Minju - ?? Hey!Haha
Yujin - I'm not impressed.
Eugene - Nonsense should be a little touching.
Eunbi - Okay!
Eunbi - What does your servant say when he breaks up with the king?
Eugene - Viking!
Tommy. - Viking?
Eugene - bye, king. King
Tommy. Oh.
Eunbi - Which floor is higher than the floor?
- A floor higher than the floor?
Tommy - The soles. Huh? Is that right?
Eunbi - Wow! Right.
Minju - Wow, how do you get it right?
CHAE WON - Wow, I'm really bad at guessing.
Yujin - More than a father, oh! This~?
Eunbi - That's amazing.
Yujin - You're smart.
Eunbi - I'll go easy now.
Eunbi - There's a good chance we won't get this right.
- What if the park gets old?
Minju - Is the park getting old?
Eunbi - I don't think I can get this right.
Eugene - I-Park...
Eunbi - Huh? It's similar.
Eugene - Kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk. I-Park Mall?
- Kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk.
Yujin - What's there?
Eugene. - Adult. Adult...
Minju - The ball is getting old.
Eugene - Park... A fight?
Minju - One... One two?
Eugene - I-Park... It's similar to I-Park?
Minju - I don't understand.
Eunbi - Park again...
Eugene - Adult Park? A 20-year-old park?
Eunbi - I don't think I can get this right. It’s too difficult. (Correct answer) Thudsak.
Minju. - Well... What? You're old.
Eunbi - What land is it with people who do everything roughly?
Minju - Do everything roughly?
Tommy, Eugene. - Land?
- Everything
Eunbi - You're all watching right now, were I looking at my cell phone alone?
- No, no, no?
- All...
- Horses... all of them?
Chaewon, Minju - All? You're not doing anything?
Eunbi - a land of people who do everything roughly.
Yujin - A hint.
Eunbi - A hint?
Eunbi - Oreung O land.
CHAE WON - Idiot!
Eunbi - Uh... Right.
Yujin - Didn't you give them all? That's enough? Oh, no, no, no, no.
Minju - Your sense is difficult.
Eunbi. - Then?
Eunbi - What if I say no doorbell in two letters?
- Nobel...
Eunbi - Oh, yeah.
Yujin - Really? I think I'm a genius.
Minju - You're a genius. You have a real sense.
Eugene - Nonsense Genius
Chaewon - Why can't I get any right?
Minju - It's hard for me, too.
Eunbi - What bus do art students take?
Minju - Art major?
Eugene - Canvas?
Eunbi - Oh, right.
- Wow
Eunbi - You're good.
EUN BI - WON YOUNG and YU JIN are so good.
Minju - You have a real sense.
YU JIN - Yeah, WON YOUNG is really good.
Eunbi - I'm really bad at this.
Chaewon - That's awesome.
Minju. - It's hard.
Eunbi - Did WIZ*ONE get all the answers right?
Minju - WIZ*ONE didn't get it right, did they?
Yoojin - Canvas, huh? I got the canvas right.
Tommy. Oh.
Chaewon - Oh, this is slow.
Eunbi - What's the Tayo bus?
Yujin - Out!
- Ahn Yu-jin, genius
Minju - Yujin is a genius.
Yujin - I saw you~
Eugene - You have a good sense.
Chaewon - I think she's stuck here.
Yujin - Chaewon looks like a middle school student.Haha
Minju - You don't look like a middle school student. You look like a kindergarten student.Haha
CHAE WON - Hey, not kindergarten.
Eugene - 12 years old. twelve years old
Eunbi - Shark half Chaewon is the same. Shark half Chaewon is the same.
Minju - She's like a real kindergarten student.
Yujin - 12 years old~
Chaewon - Don't make fun of me.
EUN BI - Oh, right. WIZ*ONE got an award today. Did you see it?
Tommy. Yes, that's right. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you. WIZ*ONE~
Eunbi - WIZ*ONE gave us an award.
Eugene. - That's right.
Eugene - We're coming back then.
When I won the Rookie of the Year award, I was just walking...
Minju. - That'sir.
Chaewon - I felt so awkward walking back then.
Eugene. Yeah, I remembered the time I was walking.
Minju - I didn't even go on a lot of promotions.
- I remember being so nervous about the timing. today
Eugene. - Right.
Eunbi. - We walked like this. We walked like this.
Minju. - That's right. Right. Memorize the timing.
- That Danve, nervous, that silhouette.
Minju - It's like yesterday.
Eugene. - That's when I just remembered.
CHAE WON - I don't think it's been that long.
Minju - Not the day before yesterday.
Not the day before yesterday.
LOL
Minju - I'm sorry.I've gone overboard.
Eugene. - Three years ago? Two years ago...
Minju. - How do you feel?
Eugene. - How long ago?
Minju - As long as you feel... 1 year
Minju - Don't you think that's enough?
- Uh, that's about it.
Eunbi - O... You're right.
Eunbi - I just think I was nervous about the first award ceremony we had since our debut.
It was. It was perfect.
Eunbi - I think I was really nervous.
Chaewon - I was really nervous.
Eunbi - I'm still nervous, but I was so nervous back then.
Minju - Every word made me really shudder.
Eugene - I'm just...
- When we said our acceptance speech when we debuted,
You and Wonyoung used to do a lot of things.
- I didn't know. So I just said, "Wow, I got an award. I love it.That's about it.
- You sometimes say things, right?
- I'm so nervous.
Chaewon and Minju. - They said they were really nervous today.
Eugene - Yeah, yeah.
Tommy. - Good job.
I was so nervous at the time of your death.
Minju. - Oh, that's right.
Minju - I think I'm really nervous.
Yujin - I always laughed next to you when you made a mistake. There was a reason why you made a mistake.
Eunbi - I have it.
Chaewon - Menba Menba
Minju - But isn't it really nerve-wracking to think of it as a live show?
MIN JU - I don't remember what to say all of a sudden because of the idea that it's going out in real time.
Eunbi - That's true, but the person in front of me does it, and then I try to do it.
I can't remember when I was listening to someone in front of me.
Eunbi - What I was trying to say is...
Tommy. - Yeah, on a slow trip.
YU JIN - Oh, right!
Eugene - So, oh, my gosh. I was like, "What should I do?"
Chaewon - This is going all at once. Once you get it wrong, you have to go again.
- That's right, that's right.
Chaewon - So it was a little bit (difficult)
Yujin - That's exactly why you're wrong.
Tommy. - That'sir.
Yujin - So what do I do? x2 But my microphone was ticking.
Tommy. - He's not coming out.
Tommy. - Thank God.
Eugene - That's why I'm doing it again.
Eugene - I'm glad to hear that.LOL
- As soon as you're done.
Eugene - I didn't think we'd get the right timing.
Minju. - That's right.
Eugene. - I knew it wouldn't work.
Eunbi - I think we've improved a lot.
Timing it out.
Yujin - Touching? Touching talk?
Minju. - That's right. It's been a while since I've talked to you.
Eunbi - I'm talking with Yujin and Wonyoung today, and they're so good. You've improved a lot. I was proud of it.
Yujin - You should look at me and talk to talk to me.
- I'm talking about me.
Minju - You've been singing since this morning.
Minju. - I'm glad to hear that. older sister
CHAE WON - Oh, you were so pretty.
Eugene - My hands are sweating.
Minju. - Why? Were you nervous?
Yujin - Nervous, nervous talk and now lol
Eunbi - We were talking about touching things.
CHAE WON - Oh, that's right. We had LASIK.
Eunbi. - That's right.
Eunbi - We were supposed to do it on the same day, but I did it first.
Minju - I envy you. I've been thinking about it. I need to think about it a little bit more.
I'm a little scared.
(Tommy's small hand size) Awesome.
Minju - There's no real lens marks.
I'm still wearing transparent lenses.
Eunbi - I was going to lie down with you on the same day.
Eunbi - I just did it first.
Chaewon - He's in a hurry.
Eugene. - Why did you do that?
Eunbi - I was in a hurry and had a hard time wearing glasses, so I did it first, and I told Chaewon about the review.
Minju - No~
Tommy - You can't wear colored lenses anymore?
Eunbi - Wouldn't it be better not to wear them anymore?
Minju - No, I came home that day, and Chaewon was standing there wearing pink sunglasses.
So, I laughed a lot. What are you talking about?
But she took off her sunglasses and showed them to you. Is she recovering faster than you thought?
CHAE WON - Are you saying you don't have to wear sunglasses?
Oh~
Chaewon - I used to wear sunglasses.lol
Yujin - How long did you wear it? One day?
Chaewon - About a day?
Minju - She was standing up there, and it was so funny.
Chaewon - I don't need to wear sunglasses.
Eunbi - I think there's dust in my eyes.
Yujin - Uhm? No, I'm not.
No? Ah!
No, I'm not.
Chaewon - Wow, your eyelashes are really long.
Eunbi - No, I think it's there.
CHAE WON - Nothing.
Eugene. - Nothing.
Eunbi - I felt it.
Tommy. - Wait, no, no, this way. x2
Tommy. This is it. This
- Oh~~~~
Chaewon - Hey, can you see that?
Eunbi - Wow...
I can't see it.
EUN BI - Yeah, it's better without this.
You're right. Wow.
Minju - It's bigger than I thought.
Eugene - I mean,
Yujin - I guess you couldn't see it because it was thin.
Yujin - Solved~
Chaewon - Solved~
Eunbi - Solved~
Yujin - No, we~ Tomorrow is already February. It's amazing.
- Wow~
Chaewon - Is it February already?
Tommy. - Already?
Eugene - Already...
Minju. - Wow.
Chaewon - That's awesome. Why is time so fast?
Minju - Time flies so fast. It is already February.
Eunbi - Already a year...
Eugene - I'm probably... Oh, my God.
Eunbi - I'm sorry.LOL
Eunbi - It's the title of the song.
Eugene. - I know. I know.
Eugene - I'm probably... Even in 2022
- And I think, 'Oh, it's already 2022?'
- Right. - I think so.
Yujin - I think it's been a year since we talked about this.
Eunbi - Oh, time flies so fast.
Minju - I think it was just yesterday that we turned on the Christmas tree and counted down.
Yujin - Oh, that's right~ That's right. x2
Eugene. - I did, but...
Eunbi - Time flies so fast.
Minju - You can't reach the light. Come here.
Yujin - That's right. It's hard, right?
Chaewon - I'm having a hard time.lol
Yujin - Switch seats?
Chaewon - But can't you see it here?
Yujin - I can see it. Instead, it's a little dark.
Minju. - I can see it.
Chaewon - It's okay! V
Minju - But, it comes in a similar color to the sofa.lol
You look like a different V LIVE from us.
CHAE WON - No, it's okay. It's okay.
Minju - Oh, that's right. This cell phone looks dark because it's under the light.
Yujin - Oh, that's right.
Eugene - That's a good thing.
Eunbi - My hair grows really fast, right?
MIN JU - Yes, I think you're growing faster than I am.
CHAE WON - Yes, but did you know that I grew a lot?
Eunbi - Doesn't it look like it's growing up?
Minju - But I grew up a lot, too.
Eunbi. - Yeah, it's been a long time.
Yujin - I think I need to put on my lips when I see this.
Hitomi - Oh, you're right.lol
- What do you think? - I need to put on my lips.
If you look at this, you don't have to put it.
Eugene - MLBB color feel...LOL
Yujin - Like that.
Minju. - Oh, that's good. Lip color?
Yujin - It's a trip! They want us to tell them the behind story.
Chae Won - It Hing Trip?
Minju - Wow, it was so much fun!
Yujin - That's right.
Chae Won - It's getting really fun.
Yujin - Isn't it almost over?
Minju - It was so delicious.
Yujin - Are you done?
Eunbi - I can only remember the delicious thing about it.
- That's right.
Minju - I really want to eat the meat I ate then.
Chaewon - I ate a lot back then.
Minju - And I remember that braised hairtail so much?
Eunbi - Um~
MIN JU - It was really good, right?
Yujin - But I'm really sorry to hear that.
We always film before our comeback.
Oh, that's right!
Yujin - I can really eat more.
Minju - I can really eat more.
CHAE WON - I'm really controlling
Eugene - Adjusted... It's...
Eugene. - Yeah. I was so sorry.
- That's right.
Minju - You're gonna take it out before you film it? I'll take it again and then I'll take it out.
Minju - I worked really hard on it. To make a comeback
Eunbi - On the first day, my face becomes like this, and on the second day, my face gets smaller.
Eugene. - Why?
Minju - First day, second day, third day.
And for the comeback kkk
Especially, if you eat salty food the day before, your face will be very noticeable.
Minju. - Oh, that's right.
Eugene - That's how it's always the second day of Ithing Trip.
Minju - I couldn't stand the beef.
Chaewon - It was delicious.
YU JIN - It was really good.
Minju - Wasn't the window from the dorm so beautiful?
- Oh, that's right.
Minju. The window was circled, and it was the real ocean. It was like a real picture.
Eugene. - The accommodation was amazing.
Minju. There's a sea in that circle.
Yujin - You were so pretty.
Minju. It was my first time, and I think it was really pretty.
The night view is so beautiful.
Eugene. - Oh, yeah, we passed the intro.
Minju. - Yeah, I just moved on.
I really wanted to try something delicious in Jeonju.
- I didn't have time.
Minju - I didn't eat anything.
Yujin - We couldn't eat it and went to Yeosu. Isn't Jeonju famous for having so many delicious things?
Eunbi - Jeonju Hanok Village has lots of delicious food.
Minju - Bibimbap, Choco Pie
Tommy. Is Choco Pie famous?
Minju - Yeah.
Chaewon - Oh, I should have eaten a lot of delicious food there.
Minju. There's a walnut stuck inside.
Eunbi - There's strawberry jam inside.
Chaewon - Oh really?
- Awesome.
Minju - White chocolate is really sweet and delicious.
Eunbi - Oh, yeah, there's a white chocolate pie.
Eunbi - These days, it's mixed up a lot.
Minju. - There's cheese, too.
Yujin - Chocolate pie?
- No, I'm not. I'm really going to have chocolate.
- Beef
- I'm feeling better.
Tommy. - Oh, really?
Eugene - Oh, of course, it was good.
Chaewon - Minju's taste.
Tommy. - You're democratized.
Minju - Let's go eat.
Yujin - Because of Minju and Wonyoung
Eugene. - Really.
Minju - Delicious?
YU JIN - Yeah, it's good.
Minju - Oh, it's time to eat cheese balls. It's time to eat cheese balls.
Chaewon - Cheese ball! It's perfect right now.
Eunbi - I mean, I'm hungry right now.
Minju - I lost so much weight because I was in Seoul.
CHAE WON - Oh, it's really a cheese ball.
Yujin - I feel it right now.
Last time we finished our online concert, we sat here.
- That's right, that's right.
Yujin - Golden Olive.
Eunbi - The golden olives are so delicious.
Eugene. - You ate Boorinkle, too.
Minju - You know that potato chicken came out.
Tommy. - Oh, yeah.
Didn't you send it to me? I saw that and I knew it.
Minju - Isn't it crunchy O?
YU JIN - Crispy O.K.
Eunbi - I want to eat chicken.
Minju - It's time to eat chicken.
Chaewon - Really
Yujin - That's right.
Yujin - But I like that. You know what I really like. Gubne pepper crunching
Chaewon - Cheese balls are perfect right now.
Tommy - I haven't tried that. Does it taste like chili peppers? -> It's spicy.
YU JIN - It's really good.
EUN BI - I love the chicken.
MIN JU - But strangely, it tastes the best when you eat with the members.
Minju - I ordered it last time when I was alone. I think it's the best when I eat with the members.
Yujin - Right. We have to eat chicken together.
Minju - Purao and Gubne pepper mayo are delicious when you eat it together.
Eunbi - You know what? Hoolala cheese buldak?
MIN JU - I used to eat hula a lot when I was young. My dad...
Yujin - I've heard of it a lot. Have you seen a lot of Hoolala commercials?
Eunbi - That's really good.
Chaewon - I feel like I've heard a lot of things.
Did you hear a lot about her?
Yujin. - Whenever she asks me to eat chicken, I ask if I have a hula.
Minju - Is that roast chicken?
Eugene - We always say we're going to eat cheese balls, and I remember hearing that.
Minju - Cheese balls are delicious.
Tommy. - You liked your wife-in-law. once upon a time
Eugene. - Oh, that's right.
Tommy. - Now?
Eugene - Supreme... I like it.
Yujin - First of all, the members don't really like it.
Tommy. - Oh, yeah.
Eugene. - Even if I ask you to eat, you don't respond much.
Eugene. - Yeah.
Eunbi - I like it.
Minju - I like it, too.
Eugene. - But you prefer something else.
Eunbi - What do you like? Coke?
Yujin - No, no, no, don't you have a favorite chicken over Supreme? Everyone?
Whenever Minju asks me to eat Supreme, I say, "Let's eat cheese balls and Boorinkle."
YEJIN - YE NA especially wants to eat Boorinkle.
- That's right, that's right.
Minju - I'm actually the main cheeseball player.
Yujin - That's right. But I like all of them, so I like all of them.
Tommy - I like Honey. Honey
Minju - Oh, right. x2 It's delicious.
Eunbi - Do you like Honey? Tommy, do you like Honey?
Tommy. Yes.
Eunbi - I'm your honey~
Chaewon and Minju. - You should eat it with tteokbokki!
Yujin - That's right. That's a good idea.
Minju - No, because of Yujin, I really want to eat rose tteokbokki.
Eugene. - It's better again.
Eunbi - Yellow whole chicken x2
Eugene - That's what we had at the ballpark.
Eunbi - I remember eating it while filming the music video for Violeta.
Minju - That's a real chicken dump.
Tommy. - NAKO keeps doing this alone these days.
- Yellow chicken?!
Yujin - It's bigger than I thought.
Tommy - number two, number three.
Eunbi - They sell tteokbokki there, too.
Minju - Fried before it gets cold. It's so delicious.
Yujin - No, I...
YU JIN - What'sir?
Chae Won - Everything I eat on set is so delicious.
Minju - The last day of the shoot. I think the chicken I eat on the last day of the music video is the best.
Tommy. - Oh, I really felt like my stomach was about to explode.
Eunbi - That last shoot, the last day, it's really good, whatever you eat.
Eugene - No, I, uh, I was getting ready for our Fiesta, and I shot our first look.
I had blue hair. She was trying to lose weight.
Eugene. - We've got a kiln on set.
Tommy - Oh, yeah! I remember.
Yujin - I've never ordered chicken gangjeong like that, and I really wanted to eat it.
So every time I look at the Gamaro River, I think of you.
- I was really, really asking how I could get them to do this.
Eunbi - I ate it a lot when I was practicing.
Minju - I'm Cropple! In the practice room, it's a little...
Some members eat less.
- The members who don't get bloated easily.
I'm so jealous of the cruffle I ate while practicing in the practice room.
Yujin - Right. Waffle~ Okay.
Chaewon - This is really driving me crazy. the real thing
Minju - I really want to eat it.
Yujin - Watermelon juice. I've never seen anyone drink watermelon juice so well in winter.
Chaewon - Watermelon juice always in winter
CHAE WON - But it's really cold, so my head is spinning. During practice.
Eunbi - I had waffles yesterday and today.
Minju - Waffles are so delicious.
Eugene - Oh, that waffle, there's a waffle machine in the house.
So, I bought croissant's birthplace and she made a lot of them.
- He told me to come and eat this. So I kept eating it.
- I showed you. You bragged about it. It was really delicious.
And then you were satisfied, and you bought another croissant.
- I bought it at a different place this time.
I'm a little less moved than I was before.
Minju - We're going to have some bar rice cakes and stuff.
YU JIN - Right, we had bar rice cake. Dip it in honey.
Minju - Oh, I'm going to go.
Eugene - What?
Eunbi. - She pressed rice.
Yujin - That's right! Rice balls! Triangular kimbap and so on.
Tommy. - Is it good? (Imagine how it feels)
Tommy - like nurungji?
Yujin - It feels like you pressed "O"? Feels like fried rice.
Minju. There was grilled cheese.
Minju - I just imagined it. How about grilled cheese balls?
CHAE WON - WOW-WOO
Eunbi - It looks so delicious.
CHAE WON - But I really want to eat it now.
Minju - It looks so delicious.
Eunbi - I want to eat raw octopus.
Minju - Everyone, but it's time for late night snack.
- What day is it today?
Sunday. 11:27 p.m.
Chaewon - Tomorrow is Monday, everyone.
Chaewon - Fighting
Yujin - I want to eat it. I'd love to eat, honestly.
- I think she'll order it soon. in five minutes
Tommy. - Did you have dinner?
Minju - I had dinner. I ate a lot today.
Minju - I ate a lot today.LOL
Eugene - I really have something to do.
Minju - Aing~
Yujin - Minju was sitting next to me in the waiting room, and she said she was full.
Minju - I'm full, Yujin, I'm full, I'm full. Why am I so full?LOL
Eugene. - I've done it seven times.
- All day long, you said I was so full.
- I asked him at first. "What did you eat?"
Oh, he just ate tortillas and yogurt. But it's not a combination that's worth getting into.
Minju - I'm gonna have breakfast.
No! Don't make excuses! NO!
Tommy. - Please be quiet.
Minju - I had tortilla for one meal a day, and I wasn't going to eat yogurt because I was full, but tortilla was spicier than I thought.
- I tried to eat it to make my mouth water, but did you eat a lot while talking to Yuri?
I got in the car so full. Hyewon said, "Do you want to have a bite?'
That's what she's doing.
Wow, so I took a bite, and it was so delicious.
- So I arrived at the garage in that condition. I was so full.
Tommy, Eugene - So, uh...
MIN JU - Is Yujin next to you? So I'm full. I said, "I'm full." And Yujin said, "LOL."
She said, "Sister, stop being full."
Tommy, Eugene - (Makes 'yes' in the shape of a hand)
Minju. - I did.Haha
Eugene. - Really.
Minju. - Finish... That's ridiculous.
Eugene - He's a difficult man.
Chaewon, Minju - (Hamburger is delicious)
Yujin - That's right.
Yujin. - She ordered mac and cheese with me.
That's why I steal it. It's really salty, but it's so delicious.
Minju - It was the saltyest food I've ever had. It's the saltyest food I've ever eaten.
Eugene - The... It was really good.
Chaewon - I'm hungry.
Eunbi - Right?
Chaewon - I'm even more hungry talking about this.
Minju. - WIZ*ONE, you're hungry?
Eunbi - And didn't you eat a lot today?
Minju - Unexpectedly, I didn't eat much.Kkkkkkkkkkkkkk of old conscience
I didn't eat a lot.
Eunbi - I did eat pork belly.
Yujin - You don't eat a lot.
Democratic - (Rationalizing)
Chaewon, Tommy. - Right. She doesn't eat a lot.
Minju. - She's short-mouthed.
Chaewon - It's small.
Minju - I'm upset.
Yujin - And she keeps leaving comments. I'm leaving a lot.
MIN JU - YE NA and I. Oh, it's the same for Chaewon.
Chaewon - I'm... Really?
Minju - I'm so full.
Minju - Oh, she was really hungry, but she said she'd be full if she took three bites.
Yujin - But you have big hands.
Eugene - That's why we end up eating everything we have left.
Eugene - I had to...
Eunbi - We ate together today. with Eugene
Chaewon - You can't leave anything behind.
Eugene. - Yeah, I took some.
Eunbi - But I'm hungry. I think I can enjoy any chicken I order.
Yujin - The chicken you buy for me
Minju - (Promotion starts) Kwon Eunbi!
Kwon Eunbi! Kwon Eunbi! Kwon Eunbi!
Kwon Eunbi! Kwon Eunbi!
Yujin - The comments are going to be unified.
Eunbi - Let me check the comments.
MIN JU - Everyone, the comments!
YU JIN - Let's unify together!
Tommy - Wow! There are so many!
Tommy. Here's your cell phone. (Purchase me chicken.))
CHAE WON - This is really it!
CHAE WON - Oh, open your cell phone.
Eunbi - What should I order?
Eunbi - Raw octopus, raw fish, or chicken, cheese ball
Tommy. - I just had raw fish.
Minju - This is it. Do you take a hint of conscience for a late-night snack or just go heavy?
Eunbi - Right, right!
Minju - But I've been on a diet for a week for today.
You said you were going to eat gopchang today. older sister
Minju. - That's right.
Eunbi - (pointing at Chaewon) Chicken?
Eugene - But to be honest, chicken is a little... Sounds great to me.
Eugene - No, I'm not.
Minju - What do you want to eat?
Eugene - But I'm all... (I think it's good.)
Tommy. - Tell me what you want to eat.
Eugene. - Uh, I don't know.
Yujin - It's ambiguous. It's budae jjigae today. I'm haha.
I don't want to eat budae jjigae.
Minju - Me too. Salmon
Yujin - It doesn't matter to me. I eat everything well.
Tommy. - I had sashimi earlier.
Yujin - I have an objection. a failure to do so
Minju. - Then not raw fish.
Tommy. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Eunbi. - One chicken and one sashimi?
Chae Won - Cool~
Yujin - Big Sonbi! Big hand rain!
Chae Won - You look the best when you order.
Eugene. There's something like that. I saw it.
There's a service where you can register your ethnic family account for delivery and ask for payment.
Yujin - Do you want to do it with me?
Eunbi - Are you doing this to your family?
Eugene. - There must be something like that.
Minju - I got a coupon last time, and it cost 5,000 won, so I was very happy.
Yujin - Oh, did you get caught? 5,000 won?
Minju - Uh-huh. She got caught.
Minju - It's 2,000 won even if it comes out a lot.
You know I don't want to use a coupon, do you?
Tommy, Eugene. - Yeah.
Tommy. - 5,000 won? Wow!
Minju - Uh, 5,000 won.
Tommy. - I'm just 1,000 won.
Minju - I can.
Minju. I got 5,000 won for the first time.
Eunbi - Are you done eating raw fish?
Eugene. - Yeah, I'm good at covering raw fish.
Minju - Except for Yena, Yuri and Hyewon, I'm going to eat everything.
Chaewon - I think I'm going to eat all the raw fish.
Yujin - Yena likes raw fish!
Minju. - You only like flatfish.
- Oh, yeah. - I only eat flatfish.
Chaewon - I really like flatfish. love of flatfish
Minju - Love Flatfish
Tommy. - What do you want? So?
Eunbi - One raw fish and one chicken
Eugene - FLEX!
Oh, the photo shoot! Minju was so pretty.
Eugene. - Really. It was pretty.
Tommy. - Agreed?
Minju - Suddenly? Haha
Yujin - No, there were four letters here. democratic news
Minju - (Thank you) I'll tell you later.
Minju - She has to work out at 6 a.m. tomorrow. WITH*ONE
Yoojin - haha with one...
Chaewon - 6 o'clock?
Minju - It's going too early. Just an hour late.
Tommy. - 6 in the morning?
Yujin - I can't even get enough energy.
Chae Won - From 6 o'clock... Exercise...
Chae-won - I work out in the morning, and the day is so hard.lol
Minju - That's right~
Chaewon - Is it normal?
Eunbi - What kind of sashimi should we order?
Yujin - flatfish, salmon, rockfish, and so on.
Minju - I want to eat salmon carefully.
Yujin - You like salmon.
Eunbi - Flatfish, Salmon
Tommy - Are you in farming or fishing?
Eunbi - Farming?!
Yujin - Wow, farming and fishing? I only saw it in the forest of animals.
Minju - I want to eat squid sashimi. Squid sashimi
Eunbi - Hey, do you want some raw squid? Us?
Eugene - (imitating the forest of animals)
Chaewon - I like anything.
Tommy - I haven't tried squid sashimi. In Korea?
Minju - Tommy, squid sashimi. It's really good.
Minju - Is there a place to do it? At this hour?
Eunbi - I have
Yujin - But I haven't tried a variety of raw fish.
Eugene - Defense! Anyone who's ever tried defensives?
Tommy. - I've been defending myself.
Minju - I don't think I remember eating raw fish.
Yujin - It's in season in winter. That's why I tried it.
Minju - Oh, really?
Yujin - When it's the season, we eat figs in the fall, it's touching.
That's how I felt when I ate the defense.
Chaewon - Who eats skate?
Minju - I want to try skate.
Chaewon - I've tried skate once.
Minju. - You're still... I only remember eating it when I was a kid.
Chaewon - I tried skate once, it's not bad, but I don't want to eat it.
Minju - Oh really?
Tommy. - What was it?
Minju - The one that smells like skate.
Eugene - I want to try it.
Tommy - I want to try it. Is it good?
You haven't tried it? Not yet?
Chae-won - They say you'll be more defensive if you eat defense.
Eunbi - Wow. That would be great for playing games.
Minju - No, isn't it coming in too quickly? You?
Minju - Oh, my gosh.
Yujin - They're funny sisters.Haha
Minju - No, I've been saying this nonsense lately, sister.
Minju - What did you hear this morning? What was that?
Minju - Oh, I really want to remember.
- I've been saying this a lot lately.
Yujin - Isn't it Bonnie Hani?
Minju - Not Bonnie Hani, but there was one more.
Eugene - Bonnie, was that yesterday?
Chaewon - Today. Today haha
Yujin - Oh, today?LOL
Minju - I said something while eating a hamburger. What was it?
Eunbi - I made you do it.
Eugene - Gil x4 Gilbert!
Minju - Oh! Oh, right.
Minju - I mean, can I say my mutual name? I didn't mean to.
Eugene. - It's okay.lol
Minju - Hamburger store was street OO, and I just read it after looking at the receipt.
She said, "It's on the road."
I did.
Yujin - No! It wasn't even "on the road."
It's just, "Road!" Kkkkkkkkkkk.
Minju - That's right. In the car. In the car.
Yujin - Right.
Yujin - So, huh? What?
Chaewon - I'm just doing it. What?
Chaewon - For your laughter!
Eunbi - Uh, it's canceled.
Minju - I don't think today is the day.
Eunbi - They said we ran out of materials. We ran out of materials.
Yujin - I guess it's a really good place.
Chaewon - This is the perfect time to order food.
Eugene. - Or Coupangites.
Eunbi - Coupangits?
Eunbi - Huh? Then, you should use your cell phone.
I don't have Coupang Eats.
Eunbi - Ahn Yujin! Ahn Yujin!
Ahn Yujin! Ahn Yujin! Ahn Yujin!
Tommy. - Coupang Eats, all we have to do is pay here.
EUN BI - Let's order chicken from Coupang Eats.
Eugene. That body is...) That body... I'm not feeling well. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, but I'm not feeling well.
What, what?x2 Chicken?
Eunbi - No, I'll order chicken now.
Tommy. - Which one? Which one?
Chaewon - Really?
How about half and half of the golden olives? Half Seasoning (Half Fried)
Eugene. - Oh, that's great.
Eunbi - Again (There's something in my eye)
Minju - How about cheese balls?
Eugene. - No, sister, I'll buy it.
CHAE WON - It's okay. the real thing
Yujin. - Hey, I'll buy it.
Minju - I can't bear to talk to you.LOL
Yujin - We'll buy it.(Empty words)
Eunbi - Yeah, then you buy it.
- Kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk.
Eunbi - I'm fine. Even if you buy it,
Eunbi - I'll enjoy your meal.
(Awkward Silence
Minju - Should we just not eat? Us? kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk.
Yujin - No, WIZ*ONE. I'll buy it.lol
Chaewon - I can't believe you're okay.
Minju - It's okay.~
Minju - (Meanwhile) Can I have your cheeseball?Haha
Eunbi - Oh, cheese ball? Okay.
Eunbi - Do you want this to be boneless? Or...
Yujin - Hey!
All of us - bones. Hey...
Eunbi - Why is it so funny when Tommy does it?
Eugene - I'll buy... crab 게
Minju - Are you still doing it?lol
Yujin. Last one. Really last one.
Eunbi. I know.
Eunbi - Look carefully. This one, this one, this one.
- No, you're not. - You're a boneless. (Not much)
Tommy. - I hate boneless.
Eunbi - (Describing menu)
Yujin - How hungry are you all?
CHAE WON - Oh, it looks so delicious.
Minju - That sounds so delicious.
Eunbi. - Then, do you want to do this? Just the one from before, like this?
YU JIN - Yes! Oh, isn't the seasoning better?
Eunbi - Oh, but that hasn't changed.
Yujin - Oh really? Then we'll go with this.
CHAE WON - It looks so delicious.
Minju - You can dip it in the sauce.
Yujin - Do you have any sauce or anything?
Eunbi - I'll add you.
Tommy - Oh, I ate a lot for dinner.
Minju - It's okay! I won't gain weight today!
Chaewon - It's okay!
Eunbi - There you go! (I think I found a menu full of spices I wanted.)
(CHAEWON, MIN JU - No Tomorrow!)
Yujin - How about a marinade and a half fried?
Tommy. - Oh~~~~~~~~~~~~~~!
Eugene. - We have it tomorrow.
Chaewon - We have tomorrow, so let's eat today.
Minju - There is no tomorrow!LOL
Chaewon - I don't want to eat tomorrow!lol
Eunbi - Cheese ball?
Eugene - BBQ Cheese Ball (here)? There is. There is.
MIN JU, TOMMY - There is. I have a cheese ball.
Eunbi - Shall we order a group?
Minju - Yeah, I love it.
Yujin - We had it back then. at the comeback show
Minju - That chocolate ball was better than I thought.
Yujin - It's like a chocolate cake skewer.
Eugene. - I remember.
Minju - I need to try it.
Eunbi - With this?
YU JIN - Yes! A group ball?
Eunbi. - Group ball? Or...
Let's just go to Domball.
Eugene - (singing Minju) Cheeseball expert!
(No answer) Okay. It's just a blanket.
Tommy - I'm eating chicken.
YU JIN - It looks delicious.
Yujin - (Eunbi)sister... It's really cool.
Minju - Are you sure you'really?
But when you eat, you have to be happy.
Tommy. - Right.
Minju - Even if I'm afraid of tomorrow... (Happily eating)
Tommy. - Don't regret it.
Eunbi - We made her do it.
Eunbi - Please, I hope it's not canceled this time.
Minju - I don't tell my teacher what I've been eating for a while.
Eugene - I'm... I have a real secret.
Reality, Eun-bi now decides - exercise tomorrow ...
Eugene - I, uh, eat me a lot before I go to the gym.
- Not to lie to you! On the day of the day, I ate chicken breast.
"What did you eat?" "That chicken breast."LOL"
Yujin - You don't ask me what I ate the other day. That's what it is.
Tommy - That's right, that's right. "What did you eat today?"
Eugene - Chicken breast. With brown rice...
Eunbi - Cancel! Cancel...
Yujin - Undeliverable area?
Yujin - Didn't you order something far away?
Eunbi. - No, I chose the closest one.
Tommy. - It's normal.
Minju - Didn't you enter the wrong address?
Eunbi - No, I did the closest one. See?
Minju - I don't think it's really today.
Chaewon - I don't think it's the day.
Tommy - You're telling me not to eat?
YU JIN - Oh, the other place is closed.
Chaewon - I don't think it's today.
Eunbi - No, you can't.ㅜㅜ
Do you want me to heat up my chicken breast sausage?
Tommy. - Well, first of all,
Minju - Do you want me to heat it up? There's chicken breast all over there.
Eugene. - There's a lot.lol
Eunbi - (???) Give up?
Minju - I ate too much last week.
Eugene - But I'm actually, it's too late.
Eunbi - Let's eat raw fish first! Let's eat and think.
Eugene. - I'm fine.Haha
Chaewon - Did you order Ahhoe?
Eunbi - Yeah.
Tommy - BBQ is here, too.
Eugene. - Oh, it's in Coupangitz.
Eunbi. - Shall we press this?
Eunbi - Press it! Press it!
Yujin - I'll buy it. I'll buy it.
Tommy. - No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yujin - Really?lol
Tommy - Uh...
Tommy. - No! No, no, no.
Eunbi - Hitomi! Hitomi!
Tommy! Jamong!
Yujin - Wow! Yellow chicken! (It looks delicious)
Eunbi - Why didn't I put Coupang Eats?
Minju. - Me, too. I'm not lying down either.
Eugene - You did it on purpose. On purposely.
Eunbi - No, I...
Eugene. Oh, my God. Goobnequin.
Minju. Yujin. Yujin is forever.
I'm Yoojin. Yeah.
Minju - Yujin is forever. He's really serious.
Eugene. - That's right.
Minju - I haven't tried it since I talked to you.
Minju - I wish your bangs were this way forever.
Chaewon - haha really?
Minju - Yeah, I love it.
Tommy. - He's cute.
Yujin - (Bangs) Can't you pay more? You?
Minju - Can you show your eyebrows? What about next time?
Chaewon - More? Can you see it? No way!!
Yujin - There's a lot more to see.
Minju. - Look. Look.
Yujin - I think it'll be cute. If you do that, you'll look like you're 12 years old.
Minju - I think it's going to be so cute.
Chaewon - Then we can't do this anymore.
Minju. - Why? I think you'll look great on me.
Chaewon - I want to look cool.
Yujin - Your bangs are so cute.
Yujin - You already... Oh, did you feel it?lol
Chae Won - No, I mean, I'm doing a panorama today, but it's not working.LOL
Tommy. - I'm sorry. I'm digesting. I ate a lot.
Chaewon - My bangs are like this.
- I didn't know your image would change so clearly.
Minju. - Change.
Eugene. - Doesn't it change?
Minju. Oh, it doesn't change, does it?
Eugene - I've been obsessed with it ever since we talked about it.
Minju - Yeah, me too. Me too.
Eunbi - It doesn't change.
Chae Won - Won't it change?
Minju - It doesn't change.
Eunbi - It doesn't change.
Minju - I don't think it's going to change.
Eunbi - You're not changing.
Tommy, Eugene - (Hand question mark)
Eugene. - Uh, what was that? Which broadcast did you do?
Tommy - Oh, yeah, I did it. What was it?
Minju - Oh, this is a Japanese broadcast!
Yujin - No!
Yujin - Weekly Idol? Idol Room?
MIN JU - This isn't a Japanese broadcast.
CHAE WON - Uh, what's this?! What was this?
Yujin - acquaintance~
Eunbi - This is Japan...
Tommy. - Was it Japan?
Chaewon - No. x2
Minju - Isn't that what Japan is? ZIP!
Tommy. - Oh, ZIP! ZIP! There's a lot.
Chaewon - What's this?
Yujin - (Reading the comments) Shindong!
Oh, that's right.
Minju - Shindonga is right. x2
CHAE WON - Wow, you remember all this. WIZ*ONE.
Yujin - That's amazing.
(To Minju) Please say, "Show! Show!"
Yujin - Starting from the left shoulder?
Minju - From the right!
Minju, look forward to next week. Show show show show!
Yujin - But you shouldn't be this bright. You have to be a little bit. Again, in Minju's version.
Minju - No~ I mean it.
- Look forward to next week too. Show show show show! Hi, how are you doing?
Minju - No, it's a little, I don't know.lol
Minju. - I'll try harder next week.
YU JIN - No. You're so understated.
Chaewon, Yujin - Moderate beauty
Minju. - Oh, but if you go there... It's kind of like a live show.
Minju - I'm nervous then?
Yujin - You must be really nervous.
Minju - I'm really nervous. I mean, obviously, I think I memorized it.
But now that you have a camera, you can't do this at all.
Especially, the important thing is,
Eugene - Right. x2
Minju - But you think I can save this, so your eyes keep turning to promporters?
- And when you're watching prompotter, your mouth gets twisted again?
I think it's hard.
Yujin - Right, but after introducing their performances,
Minju - That's right. I'm really nervous about that.
Yujin - Uh, I'm really nervous. Other people are making a comeback.
Minju. - That's right.
MIN JU - Do you know that IZ*ONE is very nervous when we introduce them?
Yujin - It's okay to be wrong! It's okay if we're wrong.
MIN JU - I want to do something really well. I want to introduce it to you.
Minju - I can't do anything when I'm nervous.
Chae Won - It's so much fun. If Minju makes a mistake,
CHAE WON - Cute.lol
Minju - haha
Chaewon - It's fun.
Minju - I won't make a mistake!
CHAE WON - WIZ*ONE will have a lot of fun. Right?
Minju - I don't want to make a mistake. I think I do it once.
Yujin - Wow, your picture quality is really good. Is it the same?
Tommy. - Why is it different?
Yujin - Oh my! Look at my bangs right now.
Chaewon, Minju. - Different brightness.
Tommy, what's going on?
Chaewon - Where have you been?LOL
Eugene - Awesome.
Eunbi - Wow, your hair is so nice.
YU JIN - Yes!
Eugene. - I set it up today.
Minju. - That's right. You know it's different when you set it up, right? My hair.
Eunbi - I think it's gonna be in Annie.
Chaewon - Today, we're on stage.
CHAE WON - I do a lot of hitting my hair. in the middle of a gesture
But you don't have a brain.~
- I don't recognize the headless sequence anymore.
Minju - Michelle~x3
I don't have a head. I did it like this.lol
Eunbi, Minju. - Good job. You were cute.
You're right. She was shaking the air like this.
Eugene - Thank you.
Eunbi - I have too much hair, so I think I need to hit it.
Yujin - Now?
Eunbi - Yeah.
Yujin - Didn't you say that you don't want to have hair extensions because you don't want to.
Eunbi - But I have to hit a lot to stick it on.
Yujin - Are you going to put it on?
Eunbi - Yeah.
Eugene - Awesome.
Eunbi - plan to extend it completely.
Minju. - There's a lot to attach.
Yujin - Michelle~
How are you, Michelle?
Eunbi - It's short.
Yujin - What time is it?
Tommy. - It's 11:47 PM.
Chaewon - Aren't you sleepy?
EUN BI - I'm going to have chicken, sashimi, and squid sashimi.
Eugene - I'm sleepy.
Eugene. - WIZ*ONE, I'm sleepy.
Minju - I'm sleepy.
CHAE WON - WIZ*ONE, but tomorrow Monday...
Tommy - So you're late, aren't you?
Chae Won - I'm doing something like that.
Eugene. - Going to work or something?
Eunbi - What's that?
Chaewon - So I'm going to... Going to school...
Yujin - Going to school!
Eunbi - Isn't it vacation?
Chae Won - Do I have to go to work?
Minju. - Looks like your brother started school, too.
Eugene. - Now... If it's January 31st,
Didn't you have spring break?
Minju - Uh, I think you're going to school.
You had an online class.
CHAE WON - Is it vacation?
Chaewon - School~
Yujin - Take the school bus and vroom~
Tommy - It's vacation.
Eunbi and Yujin - Are you on vacation?
Tommy. - Yeah.
Minju - Oh really?
Chaewon - Oh, is it vacation?
Yujin - Oh, you said you were going to school tomorrow.
College students are on vacation.
CHAE WON - Oh, but I heard you're starting school.
Chaewon - No?
Yujin - Aren't you the only college student on vacation?
Tommy - I'm applying for the college entrance exam tomorrow.
Yujin - Oh really? Minju - Wow, really?
Eunbi - School starts tomorrow.
CHAE WON - School starts tomorrow.
CHAE WON - School starts tomorrow?
Eugene. - Graduation online.
Tommy- Really? Oh, my god.
Yujin - Jongsik... They're all different.
Eunbi - Yeah, they're all different.
Eugene. - Well, every school is just online.
It's different when we do things like this.
Yujin. - She wants to go to college.
Minju. - I want to go.
Chaewon - Me too
Yujin - I really want to go to MT.
Eunbi - I really want to go.
Yujin - Really Just a Group Project
I've only heard of course.
You always read webtoons?
CHAE WON - That's right.
Minju. - That's right. That's right.
Eunbi - I remember
Minju. - You all have fantasies, right?
Chaewon - I have a fantasy.
Eunbi - When I really got into that school,
Eunbi. - It was when I didn't do it in the beginning.
Eunbi - So I went to school early.
Eunbi - But it was fun. than I thought I would at school
Eugene - When it comes to group work,
What kind of style are we?
Minju - Group project...
Yujin - What kind of style are we?
Yujin. - You look like a leader.
Eunbi - Uh, leader...
Chaewon - Driving force.. You're the driving force!
Eugene. - Captain? Promoter style?
Yujin - You're a real pushover.
Chaewon - Yeah, the momentum is amazing.
Eugene - Really
Minju - You do what you decide to do.
Eugene - Yeah.
Chaewon - if you do it, you'll just have to do it.
It's just that's it!
Minju. - So I don't care.
Eunbi - I'll do it! And start right away.
CHAE WON - That's right.
Yujin - I'll do it.
Minju - If you say "I'm going to do it~" you can do it the next day.
CHAE WON - Oh, yeah, yeah.
Eunbi - Oh, right. You saw it.
Minju. - Shall we try? I'll do it the next day.
CHAE WON - Oh, yeah. It's amazing.
Eunbi - Minju, shall we go make it? I'm making it if I do it.
Chaewon - I think it's good.
Minju - I already have a reservation.
Eugene. - Right.
Minju - Are you really going...?
Minju - Group project...
Eunbi - That face... face
Are you saying that you've gained weight?
Look, look.
Minju - Where are you going?
Eugene. - I don't get mixed up. honestly
Chaewon - I mean...
Minju - I don't understand the meaning of miscommunication.
Chae Won - Oh Dong Tong... Ha...
Tommy. - Hey.
Yujin - No, but if you say it like this,
It could be.
Chaewon - What's wrong with you?
You look happy.
You look happy. Good. Looking good.
Eunbi - I ate too much waffles.
Okay, I'm fine.
Eunbi - I lost some weight on my face.
I'm a little overweight right now.
Eugene - You look just fine.
Minju - Uh, I've got cheek fat.
CHAE WON - They're asking if you're dressed backwards.
Eunbi - This... It's not upside down.
Yujin - Isn't it V-neck?
Eunbi - It's a V-neck. Does it look stuffy here?
Minju - You've been to Fantasy Campus.
Minju. - Yeah, we went to campus.
CHAE WON - Oh, that's right. That's right.
Eugene - Oh, okay, okay.
Chaewon - Just a moment?
Minju. I've been there.
Eugene - D-DANCE!
Eunbi - Do as you please.
Yujin - The choreography was really hard.
Minju - Wow, the choreography was really hard.
Chaewon - Dae-dae-dae-dae-dae-dae-dae dance~
Minju. - We didn't have much time to prepare.
CHAE WON - That's right.
Eugene - This is... After it's over
Minju - Almost right after?
Yujin - Did you do it right away?
CHAE WON - Yes, I did.
Tommy. - I think it was September.
Minju - I'm so busy right after I'm done with my busy schedule.
Eugene. - That's right.
Minju. - A few days later.
Yujin - We had our hair done at the online concert.
CHAE WON - Oh, yeah. It was around then.
Eunbi - Oh, yeah. I had black hair.
Eugene. - My hair... around that time
Chaewon - It must have been by then.
Eunbi - That's enough for an online concert.
Tommy. - You celebrated Yena's birthday.
Minju. That day. That day.
Eugene - Didi and...
CHAE WON - Oh, right.
CHAE WON - Oh, right, MIN JU. - That's why we're
You lit a candle at the set.
Eunbi - Did we film everything in a day?
Minju - day by day
Eugene, Tommy. - One day.
Eugene - Almost like this, from dawn to dawn.
I'll do it and finish it in a day.
CHAE WON - That's right. That's right. We're done in a day.
Eunbi - We just went up and filmed it.
What's that at first?
MIN JU, CHAE WON - Mirror ball.The mirror ball?
Eugene - The thing that went up,
It was Wonyoung who went up completely.
Eunbi - Oh, right.
YU JIN - WON YOUNG's on top of it.
Eunbi - It was up there.
Eugene - We were looking around and said, "Wow, that must be scary.~"
Minju - The shooting was really fun.
MIN JU - Isn't the choreography so addictive?
Chaewon, Minju. - Good choreography.
Yujin - At first, I was really surprised.
It's so hard.
Minju - It was too difficult.
Eugene - But when I was dancing,
There's a lot of missing parts.
Eunbi - Us Us
Yujin - But at first, right, we're missing a lot.
Yujin - But at first, we'really...
We all learned the choreography.
Yujin - So I'm going to do this, this, this, this.
Minju - Divide the class.
YU JIN - Yeah, I'm cutting it in half.
YU JIN - I really worked hard.
Scissors.
Minju - Right, right. We've been working really hard.
I don't do this either.
Eugene - But get out.
Tommy. - Oh, really?
Yujin - That's why I like it, but I'm sorry...
Minju. - Good. Too bad. Yeah, right.
Eugene - Oh, if I had known...
Eugene - I did.
Eunbi - If I had known beforehand.
Eugene - This is so hard.
Eugene. - This has details. budding
Chaewon - That's right. Twice.
Minju. - It's a duck. It's a real duck.
- Breaking it in half. - That's it.
- Take my heart~
Minju - We have a lot of people.
Each song has a lot of rest.
Eugene, Tommy. - Yeah.
MIN JU - I think each song has an exceptional number of members. That's where the line goes.
Eugene - If you don't go in once,
That song won't go on.
Minju. - That's right. That's right.
Minju - Fiesta was hard for me, I...
Eunbi - Oh, right.
MIN JU - I'm sure there's a hard song for everyone. Probably.
Eugene - Fiesta When we first learned,
It was really hard.
Minju - I couldn't breathe after verse 1.
Chaewon - It was really hard back then.
Eunbi - Didn't your thighs hurt? The next day?
Eugene. - That's right.
Chae-won - She's got a bone in her body.
Minju. - It was a real egg.
- What do you think my comment... In my comment,
There's someone who's getting a cooking license.
I just thought of it. I want to be a good cook.
Eunbi - Oh, cooking?
Minju - Suddenly?
Eugene - Because in the evening... In the evening these days,
Rose tteokbokki, malatang
I'm craving this kind of this.
But when I wake up, I want to eat home-cooked meals.
CHAE WON - Oh, yeah.
I just want to eat home-cooked meals and Korean food.
Eugene. - Eventually, the delivery is a little... provocative. Korean food is coming.
Minju. - That's right. That's right.
Minju - But the salad has a lot of seasonings.
That's why
Eugene. - That's right. That's why.
Eugene - If I could cook, I'd say,
I know what I put in.
YU JIN - Wouldn't it be okay to eat it like that's?
Minju. - Yeah, but if you grill mushrooms,
Aren't you a little happy?
Eugene. - That's right. That mushroom.
Minju - I'd rather have some salad.
If the salad is a little salty, it's a little...
Eugene - Enoki Mushroom!
Minju - Uh, so...
Tommy. - Delicious.
Tommy - I've been making tortillas lately.
Chaewon - Do you make Torriya?
No, it's tortilla. It's not making dough.
Minju - Oh, it's wrapped like this. That's totally fine.
Yujin - Like this? Like that?
Minju. - Foreman. It's full.
Eugene. - I made tortilla today.
Yujin. - Nako and the two of us earlier.
- Game? - Yeah.
Minju - Ah, you said it was so much fun.
I need to try. / Tommy. - In the waiting room?
Yujin - Oh, is this the game you keep asking?
Tommy. - He's in the waiting room.
Eunbi - The game I told you to play in the waiting room.
Chae Won - He's really fun at the game.
Eunbi. - Nako...
Eunbi - I cast Nako with her.
Eugene. - Is it on the switch? / - Yeah.
(Game title: Overcooked!)
Eugene. - You learn vegetables first.
Eugene - I love bean sprouts.
Eunbi - I'll let you know.
Minju - Ah, bean sprouts are delicious!
Chaewon - Really?
Tommy. What? / Minju. - Host greens. / Tommy. - What's that?
Eunbi - Why did you say you were going to learn?
You don't trust me?
Minju - Do you know it comes with chicken feet?
Yujin - Do it! / Eunbi. - Yeah.
- Eugene, please.Kk
Minju - That bean sprout...The bean sprout brother?
Chaewon - I want to eat chicken feet.
Tommy. - Do you have a brother? - Eugene. - Uh! Chicken feet!
Tommy, do you have a sister?
Eugene - No, not my brother.
Minju - Vegetables similar to bean sprouts
Eugene - thinner, smaller head,
Minju - It's a little smaller than bean sprouts.
Eugene - Thin... Oh, soft... Maramara.
Minju - No, you're...Kk
Chaewon - Maramara Maramara Maramara
Yujin - Add to Maratang...
Tommy. - There's something like that?
Eugene. - Yeah, I really like it.
When I was young,
Eunbi - It's in bibimbap.
Tommy. - What was your name? / Eugene - Host
Minju - bean sprouts, uh...
Eugene - That's a little... Elementary school? Middle school?
Oh, I was in elementary school. in the senior year of elementary school
Minju - No, Minju when you're in it.
You know, instead of going to private academies, you know,
Eugene - I don't know anything like DIY.
Anyway, the center? Should I say this?
I went to a place by the way.
Tommy. - Is this it? - Minju. - Oh, this, this.
Eugene - I had a meal there.
It's like a school lunch break.
Tommy. - Huh? Isn't it just baking?
Minju - I feel a little skinny.
Eugene - bean sprouts, there are bean sprouts.
Eugene. - It was a good restaurant. That's what I did.
I was so touched.
Tommy - Do you eat a lot? Minju - She eats a lot.
Eugene. There was stir-fried spicy pork.
The bean sprouts are really...
Minju looks like bean sprouts. / Isn't that Tommy?
Eugene. - I've been taking it about eight times.
Bob and the teacher were like,
Minju. She's thinner than bean sprouts.
Eugene - You praised me.
"Wow, I eat vegetables well, too."
Tommy, your head is small. Oh, my head is small. Minju, your head is small.
Eugene - I've been like that ever since.
I think I've come to like bean sprouts.
Minju - It's really good.
Eunbi - Did you grow up because you ate vegetables well?
Eugene - No, I don't like vegetables.
Minju - I like the host in the chicken feet.
Eugene - I didn't like paprika.
Chaewon - Oh really? Paprika is really good.
Tommy - Did you like milk?
Eugene - I'm Chocolate Milk
Eunbi - What about white milk?
Eugene. - I didn't like it. - Eunbi. - Oh, really?
Eugene - I'm here with bread.
I liked it when I ate it.
Eunbi - Oh really?
Eugene - I hated white milk.
Minju - This is all a lie.
Eunbi - Is it just a big man?
Chaewon - I guess so.
Eugene - I saw that.
Eugene - It's a complete genetic material.
Eunbi - Oh...
Eugene. - The acquired impact is...
Eunbi - Is your mother big?
Eugene - It's a little too big.
Eunbi - You're a little tall, aren't you?
Eugene. - Yeah.
Eugene. - Yeah, you're big. I think it'sir.
Minju - I'm just father and mother.
I think it's a key. Me too.
Eunbi - Oh really?
CHAE WON - Yeah, me too.
Eugene. - That's right. He's totally genetic.
Chaewon - Genetic is a bit important...
Eugene. - He's got a big impact.
Minju - I couldn't drink white milk when I was young.
Eunbi - Me too
Minju - I didn't drink chocolate milk.
Me too. Do you know what that straw is?
CHAE WON - Yeah, I haven't had white milk.
Minju - Sometimes banana milk?
The straw in the chocolate?
CHAE WON - Oh, I always carried it to that school.
Eunbi. - What's that?
Minju - That's... The O
Minju - I remember.
Eugene - In that straw,
It's the one with the chocolate.
Minju. - Oh, this is red.
It's just like this.
Yujin - So if you wash it like this,
Minju. - If you drink...
Tommy - So if you drink water like that, you'll just...
Yujin - Chocolate water?
Minju - Chocolate water? That's a little...
Eugene. - It's not going to taste good.
Eunbi - Once upon a time at school
Eunbi - Back in the day, at school,
Bring the milk to the box,
Eunbi - You have to drink milk like this.
Yujin - That's right!
Eunbi, you always drink milk in elementary school.
Eugene. - That's right. That's right.
Tommy. That's right. That's right.
Eunbi - I covered my nose with one hand and drank.
Minju - But that's chocolate milk.
Weren't you able to change it?
Eugene. - That's what he says these days. But I wasn't.
Eunbi - Uh... We weren't.
Minju - So I had chocolate milk. so
Eunbi - Wow, that's awesome.
Yujin - Really? It wasn't me either.
Minju - Uh, when you order,
Minju - I could do it with chocolate milk.
Eunbi - But there are people who drank it all and didn't.
I'm telling him to fold it.
Eunbi - Fold it...
Minju - Right, everyone who ate all these snacks...
Minju. - Right.
Eunbi - So I forced myself to drink like this
I folded it in.
Eugene - I just didn't let him choose.
It was just an absolute necessity.
Eunbi - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yujin - Milk Meal
Minju. - That's right. That's right.
Chaewon - So the straw
I used to carry it all the time.
Minju. - Yeah, I carried a lot of this straw.
Eunbi - Oh, really, I'm Jetty.
Eugene. - Straw, Jetty, Jetty.
Minju - Agetti Admitted
Eugene. - Jetty, you want me to put in a little.
Eunbi - I used to burn it two times every day.
Minju, you know it's really good if you get two of those, right?
Eugene. - Yeah, we have to do two.
Minju. - Yeah, two. One is a little...
Minju - Less sweet
Eugene. - Right.
Eunbi - To be honest, there's a WIZ*ONE who's upset.
I saw it. I think it's there.
Eugene - It's almost like...
CHAE WON - I'm sure there are.
Eugene - I'll be done next month.
Tommy. Wow.
Chaewon - Really?
CHAE WON - Good job~ - Eugene. - Good job.
Tommy. - When did you start? - Eugene. - I...
Eugene - Um... My Little Television
It was about time.
Yujin - Violeta, is that it?
Yujin - About that?
Minju - Uh, Chaewon's stomach is ringing.
Tommy. - Huh? Hungry? - Eugene. - Goruk?
Minju - I'm hungry~
Tommy. - You should eat a lot.
Chaewon - Who is it? - Minju. - Who are you?
Chaewon - Is it thundering?
Minju - Yeah?
Eunbi is doing zero exercise, and she's experiencing a slump.
Eunbi-so I don't know if I should stop or continue.
I'm thinking about it.
Eunbi - Of course we have to keep going.
Minju. - Why? It could be too hard.
Eugene. - Why? But it's just...
Eugene - Vocational Exercise... Exercise by profession
Maybe you're talking about it.
Eunbi - I think I have to get over it.
Eugene - Wow.
Eugene - I can do that's possible.
Eunbi - There's no waiver. our friend
I want you to get over it and work hard.
Minju. - Yeah, but...
Eunbi - I rest when I'm having a hard time.
Eunbi, I hope you get up again and work hard.
Minju - It's important to rest well. / Eugene - That's right.
Chaewon - It's really important to rest.
Chewon - You can take a break.
Eunbi- I'm not good at resting. It's really important to rest.
Minju - I'm tired of running too much.
Eunbi - Minju taught me how to rest a long time ago.
Minju - Uh, how... What did I tell you?
Eunbi - You really need to rest.
Don't do anything. Stay still.
Minju - Oh, yeah. That's right.
Eunbi - I'm not good at staying still.
Minju - But when you really rest,
You're just lying down. in the room
Eunbi - That's right.
Minju. - We need that kind of time. Guys.
Eunbi - I need it. I really need it.
Eugene - But I'm curiously,
You're so busy that you suddenly take a break.
I don't really like the feeling.
Yujin - So you can work out,
Minju - Something's right. That's right.
Eugene. - You can take a lesson.
Tommy. - We have to do something.
Eugene - Something... It's kind of.
Minju. - That's right. - Eugene. - You have to do something.
Eunbi. - That's right, that's right.
Minju - 2 lessons on a day without schedule
Chaewon - Whatever you do, just grab the lesson.
Tommy. - Me, too.
Eugene - There needs to be something.
Minju. - The lesson needs to be in the morning to wake up.
Otherwise, you'll be too lethargic.
Tommy. - It's a waste of time.
YU JIN - Oh, yeah. Isn't that a waste?
Eunbi. - That's right. - Tommy. - Oh, that's too bad.
Minju - I'm wasting my time.
Eugene. - Especially the more we do it, the more we see it'
Minju. - That's right. That's right.
Eugene - If we practice,
So the next practice... You'll see it on the next stage.
Minju. - That's right. That's right.
Eugene - So when something passes,
Do you feel sorry for him?
Eunbi - That's right.
Eugene - So...
Minju. - It's so early in the morning.
We've been moving since dawn.
Minju - something's not happening and lying down.
I think that's a waste of time.
Eugene. - I was busy, and then...
Chaewon - Right. - Eunbi - So...
Yoojin - Oh, that's exactly how it feels after the college entrance exam.
Chaewon - Oh really? - Eugene. - Oh, I see.
Chaewon - Oh, I see.
MIN JU - Do we feel like we're done with the awards ceremony?
Chaewon - I think she's similar to us.
You're right. Well, when you take the college entrance exam,
They're all working so hard.
Minju. - Right.
Minju - Well, if it's over, it's a little too much
Eugene - My friends have come to see me.
They're friends who take the college entrance exam.
Chaewon - Wow, you're right.
Eugene - My friends are taking the college entrance exam, too.
Eunbi - Wow, you really grew up a lot.
Eugene. - I mean, sister.
Minju - Eugene's grown up.
Eunbi - When I first saw you, middle school student? High school student...
Yujin - Middle school student!
Eunbi. - She was in middle school. Yeah.
Minju. - That's right. I was a middle school student.
Yujin - Isn't it amazing?
Chae Won - But I used to be in high school
You went out to play. We're going to do it's going to be...
Yujin - That's right. When you entered the school!
Tommy. That's right.
Eunbi - During IZ*ONE Chuu~
Chaewon - That's awesome. - Wow... - Wow.
Eunbi - That's when we made flowers.
Eugene's giving me flowers. / Minju. - Right. That's right.
Chaewon - That's awesome.
Minju - Yujin entered the school, right?
Yujin - It was an entrance!
Eunbi - Oh, Yujin, you've grown so much.
Yujin - You always go to graduation.
I said, "Hey, Yujin is going to the graduation ceremony."
Do I just have to go now?
Eunbi - What Yujin ate when she entered school...
Tommy. Oh, black bean noodles.
Eunbi - I can't forget the cream shrimp.
Tommy - Oh, really! - Eugene. - That's right.
Chaewon - Cream shrimp was really good.
Tommy - Life Cream Shrimp.
Minju - I really want to eat it! suddenly
Tommy. - Right. - Chaewon. - So...
Eunbi. - It's all about eating.
Eugene - So we end up eating.
Tommy. - Eventually eating.
Minju - Why did you end up eating again?
Eunbi - Are you coming to my college graduation?
Chaewon - I have to go. - Tommy - I have to go.
Yujin - When?
Eunbi - But I think I'll be over 30.
Yujin - I'll go now. I'll dress up nicely.
Minju. - We have to go.
Chaewon - We'll go. We'll go anytime.
Chaewon - I'm going to bring a bouquet.
Yujin - And you have to do it around that time.
Eugene. - I might not be online.
Eunbi - Oh, that's right. - Tommy. - Oh, yeah.
Tommy. - Really.
Eugene - I'll do it for that.
Time really flies.
Eunbi - Oh, yeah. Did you go to school with Minju?
Eugene. - Right.
Minju. - Eugene. Yeah, that's right.
Chaewon - That's right.
Minju - Eating bread with Eugene at the canteen.
I still remember.
Eugene. - That's right.
Minju. - Something's missing.
Eugene - I recently found out that the name was
You remembered his name.
Yujin - Matstar
Minju - Oh, Matstar. That's right. That's right.
Eugene - I really remember the name
It didn't go out. Really. / Eunbi. - They said it's a food star.
Minju - No, after I'm done, together.
Minju - I loved the feeling of eating it.
Eugene - That's right.
Eunbi - Originally... That's right.
Minju - You always leave work alone...
I was leaving school.
Eunbi - Right, right. And the bread you eat at the canteen.
It's really good.
CHAE WON - Yeah, that's right.
Minju - But it was really delicious.
Minju - I was in the microwave with Eugene.
I heat it up and it's going down.
Minju - Something felt good.
Eunbi - There's that hamburger.
Minju. - Yeah, that's it. Matstar.
Eunbi - You've changed your name.
Minju - Cheese bread?
Minju - No, it'll be the same.
Chaewon - What is it? - Eunbi. - Hamburger shape?
Minju - Hey, it's a bit of a croquette.
Eunbi - It wasn't croquette. It was a hamburger.
Minju - Oh really?
Eunbi - There's that, there's this long one.
Minju - Chiabata
Eunbi - No.
Minju - Oh... Maybe it's something else.
Eunbi - Khmmm
Chaewon - I used to eat a lot of dumplings.
Eunbi - Did you sell dumplings?
Chaewon - Dumpling...Yes! I sold dumplings!
Minju - I didn't sell dumplings. We've got a lot of us.
Eunbi - Oh, they sell dumplings.
Eunbi - That's amazing.
Chaewon - 6 dumplings, dung, dung, dung, dung, dung.
It's like this.
Eunbi - Our school doesn't sell carbonated drinks.
You sold it with me.
Minju - You don't sell soda, do you?
Chaewon - I didn't sell soda.
Minju - I have that mango juice.
Minju - Delmon0 or something you sell...
Minju - I've had a lot of that.
Eugene - Delmont. - Eunbi. - She's really good. You
Eugene. - I know.lol
Eunbi - She's good at sticking her finger out every time she does something.Kk
CHAE WON - Delmon, tell me more.Kk
Eunbi - ice cream was really good.
Minju. - That's right. That's right.
CHAE WON - Right.
Tommy - I had a canteen and a convenience store.
Eunbi - Ah! - Minju - Huh? To school? / Tommy. - Yeah.
Eunbi - There was a school with convenience stores.
Minju - You're the best! - Eunbi. - Yeah, I envy you.
Tommy. - It was great.
Yujin - When I go to Japan,
There's a convenience store at the station.
Minju - That's right. - Eugene. - Right?
Tommy. - Oh, yeah. - Eugene. - So...
Yujin - That's why I go to eat every day.
Eunbi. - Right.
Yujin - I'm always drinking soda from the vending machine.
Tommy. - Right.
Eunbi - I'm going to go to the Japanese convenience store and we're gonna...
Eunbi - Odeng, the one with the mochi inside the married couple.
Eunbi. - They sell it. - Yeah.
Eunbi - So
Eunbi - It was so delicious.
I ordered the internet and tried it.
Eunbi - With fish cake? /
Tommy. - That's it? Wow.
Eunbi - It was so delicious.
Minju - Unnie~
Chaewon - Oh, that's good.
Minju - This is Nako's mother.
It's my favorite.
Eunbi - This is really good.
Minju - You sent me chocolate as a gift.
Chaewon - Can you give it to me? Minju - I'm done eating.
Minju. - Thank you, mother. Thank you~
Eunbi - Something's light inside.
Eunbi - Soft
Chaewon - Thank you, Minju. - Thank you.~
Eunbi - Ahjjang Mama
Chaewon, Minju - Thank you.~
Chae Won - Please~
Minju - It was delicious!
Chaewon - Thank you so much.~
Eugene. - Karamucho.
Minju - I ate it as soon as I woke up this morning.
Chaewon - It's already 12 o'clock. It's February.
Minju - Huh?
- Wow~~~
Minju - Congratulations on February!
Chaewon - Be happy in February, too!
Tommy. - We started February together.
Minju - Be happy.~
Yujin - Be Happy~
Minju - February with us!
Tommy. - Together. - Chaewon. - We started together.
Minju - Welcome. It's already February!
Tommy - I think my stomach hurts.
Minju - Suddenly?
Minju - Are you okay?
Tommy - Uh-huh.
Minju. - Because you're hungry? - Tommy. - No, no, no.
Eunbi - I'm hungry.
Tommy - I just ate a lot.
Minju - Hungry makes me hungry.
Eugene. - That's right.
Eunbi - February Clap Clap Clap
CHAE WON - It's February. Really.
Eunbi - I bought a case. Isn't it cute?
Eugene - Cute, Smile.
Minju - Cute!
Chaewon - Look at your nail art.
Eunbi. - Ta-da! Twinkle twinkle.
Eugene - Gao!
Chaewon - Gao-ao Dance!
Tommy. - I really removed my nails.
Yujin - I mean, you were so long.
Eunbi - It's very... No, but Hitomi told me...
Last time we practiced,
How did you grow your nails? That's what I said,
One day I saw Hitomi's nails and they were really long.
Chaewon - You didn't extend your nails, did you?
Tommy - I wanted to be like you, so...
Eunbi - I was totally amazed.
Chaewon - You didn't extend your nails, did you?
Tommy. - I didn't extend it.
CHAE WON - Wow.Why is it so long?
Minju. I only did gel and color.
My fingernails are very weak. It's soft right now.
Minju - Nails / Chaewon - Oh, yeah?
Minju - Right? It must have been really bad.
- Wow. - Tommy. - It's really long, isn't it?
Chaewon - What's wrong? - Minju. - Right? I'm scared.
So when you change your clothes, it breaks if you do something wrong.
Eunbi - I'm a little weak. Oh, yeah.
Minju - I shouldn't do my nails for a while.
Eunbi - This... Wow, is this really not uncomfortable?
Tommy. - It's uncomfortable. - Eunbi. - Oh, it's uncomfortable?
Minju. I'll lend you a remover.
Didn't you take it?
Tommy. - I'm gonna clean it up. - Eunbi. - Cut some?
Tommy - Yes. - Eunbi - What's bothering you?
Chaewon - Remover? Suddenly a remover?
Tommy. - Well... Everything's uncomfortable. / Eunbi. - Oh, really?
Minju. - No, on your fingernails. - Chaewon. - Acetone?
Minju - Yes, ahacetone
Eunbi - I think I'm most uncomfortable with lenses.
Chaewon - No, I never used it on my nails.
Minju - I lent you something on your clothes.
Chaewon - Yeah, I gave it back.
Minju - Did you give it back? Where did he put it?
Tommy - It's fine when you're wearing it. - Eunbi. - When you're taking it out.
Tommy - It hurts so much when you take it out.
Eunbi - You need to pull your hand out here.
Tommy. - Yes, here.
Eunbi - That's a little bit of a skill.
CHAE WON - Yeah, long nails can't take out the lenses.
Minju - I hate it so much.
Chaewon - So I did LASIK!
Minju - I cut my nails here to get rid of the lens.
Tommy - You cut your nails? - Minju. - Yeah, I got my nails cut.
I was so frustrated that I had my nails done, but I just cut them.
Tommy. Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhh.
Minju - I'm going to take off my lens.
Minju - I'm not doing it for long. Again.
Tommy - But is it okay if I keep growing it?
Minju - So, you're the one who'
Your nails must be really strong.
Tommy - Thinning...
Chaewon - Give me a break. a break
Eunbi - But when you rest, it's cut off.
It's getting too thin.
Tommy. - Oh, really?
Eunbi - So I always say that.
So you need to apply a thin layer of transparency.
Tommy - Oh... Is that right?
Yujin - Try it completely short.
Eunbi - I used to be really short.
Eugene - Not at all! Not...I think we'll do that.
CHAE WON - Right, you were really short.
Eunbi - I couldn't grow my nails at all in the beginning.
Yujin - Really? - Chaewon. - You were so short.
Totally short. / Minju. - Right, right, right.
Eunbi - I'm not out of flesh. My fingernails.
Tommy. What? / Chaewon. - Yeah. It was really short.
Eunbi - I didn't grow my nails well.
Yujin - Did you open it? Isn't that right?
Eunbi - With your hands...
Eugene - Oh, yeah.
Yujin - Like this
Eunbi - Bad Habits
Oh~
Eunbi - I can't grow my toenails now.
Yujin - How do you do your toenails? Why? Why?
Minju - It's very mini-mini-mini.
Chaewon - Wow, you're not sick?
Yujin - Do you always cut it short?
Chaewon - How... - Minju - I think she's going to bleed.
Eunbi - I want to cut it like this.
Eunbi - So, like this, out of the flesh.
If your toenails stick out like this,
Chaewon - It's too short. - Eugene. - It's uncomfortable.
Minju - Doesn't it hurt too much if you cut it short?
I always leave this much behind.
Eunbi - I've been like this since I was too young.
Minju - Really? - Chaewon. - Really? You look sick.
Eunbi - But I want to grow this.
So you went to get your nails done?
You want to get this, Teddy?
But it's too short.
He told me to grow it out.
Chaewon and Minju. - Really?
Eunbi - Okay~
Tommy. - When did you last rest?
Eunbi - I never rested.
It's transparent, but when you rest,
Eunbi - But I don't think I've been resting lately.
I think I kept doing it.
Eugene. - Oh, yeah.
Minju. - Take a break. Concert.
Eunbi - It was a little short. I cut it this time.
Tommy. - Yeah, I think so.
Eunbi - It's getting shorter, right?
Minju - You should get some rest. You have long nails.
Chaewon - Really?
Minju. - I let it go.
Chaewon - Yeah.
Eugene - If you go to Caribbean Bay or Ocean World,
Do you know what it is on the floor?
Eugene - Don't slip.
Minju - If you fall down there,
Do you know it's real?
Eugene - Don't slip.
Chaewon - Anti-slip!
Eunbi - Listen to the sound.
Yujin - It's kind of like sand.
Minju. - That's right.
Minju - Maybe it's because you're relaxed?
Minju - My eyes are closing.
Eunbi - Is that Yena's hat?
Eunbi - That blue pink yellow thing?
Minju - Is that right? Oh...
Eugene. - I think I used it before.
Eunbi - Oh really? Surprising.
Eugene. - Hip hop. What concept? When you take a scene,
Eunbi - Cotton candy hat. Cotton Candy Hat
CHAE WON - That's amazing. I think it's really unique.
Eugene - I'm actually...
Eugene - I think I'm a little sleepy right now.
Tommy. - What?
Minju - I'm actually...
Tommy - You're not going to eat?
Minju. I was actually going to sleep as soon as I got in.
Yujin - Thank you for your hard work.
Tommy. - Huh? - Chaewon. - Oh, my God.
Yujin - Oh my gosh!
Eunbi - It doesn't matter. We can enjoy it.
Chaewon - Huh? WIZ*ONE
Chaewon - Are you okay?
Eunbi - It's okay!
Chaewon - WIZ*ONE! I can't see the chat window.
Uh, uh, here's... I will go.
Chaewon - It was so hard sitting here.
Eunbi - Yeah, sit here, Chaewon.
Eugene. - No.No, no, no, no!
Yujin - I'll eat it' I didn't think it right!
Eunbi - Go! Don't!
Eugene - I did something wrong.
Eunbi. - I'm going to read the comments with this.
Minju - WIZ*ONE must be sleepy.
Yujin - Right?
CHAE WON - Oh, but tomorrow is Monday.
Chaewon - You should go to bed early.
Yujin. - Huh? Slowly? Cheap rice?
Then unnie, then haha
CHAE WON - You're not the only one.
Yujin. - This is the only thing you can do.
What did you say to me?
CHAE WON - No.
Yujin - Are you sleepy? Honestly?
Minju - My eyes are a little closed.
Eunbi - I think I'm going to eat and go to bed.
Guys?
Minju - Eat and sleep.
Eunbi - What should I do?
Minju. I don't think I'd ever eat and sleep.
If it's the same, it's the same.
Minju - I almost fell asleep as soon as I got here.
Tommy. - Where's the delivery now?
Tommy. - Where are you?
Chaewon - You two sleep~
Eugene - Oh, that high school student...
You're not supposed to do a late night broadcast?
Uh, no, no.
A high school student should not be over 12 o'clock?
Minju - Yujin is still a high school student, right?
Eugene - Yes! - Minju. - Oh...
Tommy. - Are you going? Are you going to go...?
MIN JU - Oh, my gosh~ Our high school student~
Minju - I was in high school, too.
Eunbi - When was high school student?
Minju - Wow, when IZ*ONE made their debut,
But you were 18.
Eunbi - You're so young. - Minju. - Yeah.
Yujin - Were you 18? - Minju. - Yeah.
Eunbi - When will you be 24?
Minju - She's a decent adult.
Eunbi - I made my debut when I was 24.
Chaewon - I'm 22 now!
Chaewon and Yujin - Twenty two~
Minju. - Twenty-one.
- Tommy. - Twenty-one. - Eugene. - Nineteen.
Eunbi - Hitomi, are you 21?
Tommy - Yeah. - Chaewon. - Wow!
Minju - Hitomi... I can't believe he's twenty-one.
Chaewon - No way. No way.
Minju - Time flies.
Yujin - Twenty One~
Tommy. - No way? / Chaewon. - Uh-huh.
CHAE WON, YU JIN - AUEE 2NE1
Chaewon - ASMR...
Minju - Oh, I'm looking at your fingers.
I'm really sleepy.
Eugene - I have really big hands.
Minju - I'm taller.
Tommy. - I'm really small.
Tommy. - Really.
Eunbi - Wow~
Yujin - Uh, we're kind of like this. If you do this,
I don't think it's going to be cool. It's a bit?
Eugene. - This is how you do it. like this
CHAE WON - Oh, come on.
YU JIN - That sounds cool.
Minju - Let's do it.
Yujin - No, it's round.
Chae Won - Circle!
Tommy. - How? - Chaewon. - Make me...
Minju - Round. - Tommy. - Oh?
- Minju. - Here we go!
Tommy. - Which side is it? Is it chicken?
Chaewon - What should I do with this?
Eugene. - Take it off one by one.
Isn't it pretty?
Chaewon - Okay, Hana~ - Eunbi - How?
Eugene - One / Minju - Two / Tommy - Three
Yujin - You have to press the button there.
YU JIN - Yes!
Minju - Thank you!
Yujin. - One, um, Ppa! Um... Pa! Is that it?
Go! Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Pa!
Minju - It's kind of full.
Yujin - Oh, do you remember that?
CHAE WON - Oh, you're right. - Tommy. - It's in full bloomed.
CHAE WON - Oh, this is from the trailer!
Tommy. - What do we do?
Minju - 10,000 members?
Tommy - I was alone like this. I was a member of 10,000.
Chaewon - Oh, do you remember this?
Eunbi - 10,000 hearts!
Minju- I was a member of 10,000. One of my hands is me.
Eugene. - I don't remember. But
Tommy. - I mean, something like this.
Eunbi - 10,000 of these. I'm at the hotel.
In the bathroom with you.
MIN JU - Oh, sister! - Eunbi. - Do you remember?
Yujin - Do I have to lower it like this?
Eunbi - Like this? How do you do it?
Minju - I was an early member.
Eugene - It was like this. So
Minju. - Like this? Like this? This is it.
- And Sakura was sitting inside.
Tommy. - This is what I did this.
Eugene - I think we just need one person to do this.
Tommy. - Do you want me to do it?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- One, two, three, four, ten thousand!
Tommy. - Did you see that? - Minju. - Can you see it?
Chaewon - This is what it's like this is it.Kk
Eugene. - This is what it was. Just.
Eunbi - 10,000 hearts. Shall we say "Umbba"?
Eugene. - Oh, good.
- Start
10,000 hearts. Um, um, um, um, um, um, yeah.
- Mm-hmm. - What do you say?
- Tap tap tap tap tap. - Gross?
- What? - Gross.
Isn't it cool?
Chaewon - Then the raw fish is here.
Tommy. - Are you going to sit there?
YU JIN - Yes!
Chaewon - Family photo?
Tommy. - Suddenly?
Yujin - my sister Eunbi...
Family picture like Eunbi unni
- Huh? - One, two, one, two...
- All right. - All right.
Three~
Chaewon - I can't do this.
Eunbi - Tommy's better these days.
Yujin - Hitomi's feeling. Hitomi's feeling.
CHAE WON - Ahitomi. Okay. Okay.
Tommy. Oh, my eyebrows.
CHAE WON - 1, 2, 3! The zodiac sign!
- For band~
Tommy. - What's this?
Eunbi - Isn't it like Hitomi?
Tommy. - No, no.
Eunbi - WIZ*ONE food is here.
Tommy. - Raw fish is here.
Minju - I'll bring it.
Tommy. - Oh? It's his favorite sushi restaurant.
Eunbi - Really?
Tommy. - Yeah.
Chae Won - This WIZ*ONE... I'm hungry.
You could be hungry.
Eunbi. - Yeah.
Chaewon - Raw fish...
Chaewon - What should we do? Do you want me to show you what I eat?
Tommy. - Uh, here's...
Minju - Modum Mature Set!
Tommy. - Hehe. I love this place.
Eunbi - He likes it. Here.
Minju - Oh, really? / Tommy. - Yeah.
EUN BI - Oh, here's this.
Tommy. - Yeah. Just stay here.
Minju - This place is so delicious.
Tommy. - Is there abalone?
Eunbi - WIZ*ONE / Tommy - Wow~
Eunbi - We're going to...
Tommy. - Do we have to go? - Minju. - The meeting's here.
Chaewon - We have to go eat.
Tommy - I'm going to go eat.
Minju. - Huh? Oh, focus.
Eunbi - We'll enjoy your meal.~
Chaewon - I'll enjoy it.
Eunbi - Bye~
Chaewon - WIZ*ONE~
Minju - Thank you for today.
Chaewon - Good night. - Tommy. - Suddenly?
Minju - Good night~